JENNINE PUNZONE

http://cargocollective.com/jenninepunzone https://linkedin.com/in/jennine-punzone (C) 516-818-1038 jennine@optonline.net

Seeking Front End Developer position with a focus on UI / UX development to utilize my 6 years of experience, strong attention to detail, and ability to solve problems through creativity. Project management and execution of applications showcases originality and incredible work ethic.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, React Native, GIT, Github, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, the command line, Adobe suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

Keepers Unlimited, Inc.

01/2014 - 05/2016

Art Director/Designer/Social Media Manager

- Visual Branding: Implemented and executed vision for brand identity, social media content, photography, advertising.
- Directed creative development across multiple social media platforms.
- Attention to detail and the understanding/experience to oversee a visual campaign from concept to production.
- Website and Inventory Management: Managed and maintained the primary websites and demonstrated expertise in Web content, development and design.
- Marketing: Broke new ground with innovative creative concepts and transformational user experiences.

Saatchi & Saatchi 2/2012 – 8/2012

Freelance Art Director

- Developed original creative solutions for marketing and objectives, while maintaining creative, technical and brand standards.
- Projects included digital campaigns, onsite banners, Web sites and/or landing pages, segmented email, social media, & print for clients such as Trident, Capri Sun, Enfamil.
- Managed multiple creative projects effectively and efficiently while maintaining priorities, deadlines, and deliverables in a fast-paced environment.

Momentum Worldwide 2012

Freelance Designer

• Developed, revamped and reformatted banner and website design for William Grant & Sons Inc.

G2 Worldwide 8/2011 –11/2011

Freelance Designer

• Conceptualized and executed package design for ITCAN. Brands including du Maurier, Peter Jackson, Players, Kent & Action Against Hunger.

JENNINE PUNZONE

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Get Some Tail 2016

Front End Developer

• Built a fun web app that allows users (men) to adopt a dog specific to the kind of girl they would like to find.

- Developed using HTML, CSS, AJAX, API's Javascript, JQuery and Firebase. Solely responsible for the Concept, Design, CSS, HTML, and Firebase
- https://github.com/jen-fong/dogadoptionapp / https://rocky-bastion-31267.herokuapp.com/homePage.html

Bet the Future 2016

Front End Developer

- A social network microbetting application which allow you to make fun bets with your friends.
- Developed using HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQUERY, Node.js, Sequelize, MySQL, Passport.
- Solely responsible for the Concept, Design, CSS, HTML, and Sequelize
- https://github.com/eHatz/group2-Bet / https://heroku-link

Crystal Collector 2016

Front End Developer

- Created a fun and interactive game in the browser that dynamically updates the HTML with JQUERY.
- Developed using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and JQUERY.
- Application was built using Express.js, Node.js, MySQL, Sequelize, Handlebars
- https://github.com/jenninep/RPG-Game / https://tranquil-thicket-50619.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

Rutgers University

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development: October 2016

Miami Ad School

Art Direction: 2009 - 2011

Stony Brook University

BA in Fine Arts & Communications: 1993 - 1997

HONORS/AWARDS

- Applied Arts Magazine, Bump a Smoke, 2011 Applied Arts Student Awards contest winner
- Mobile App Goes Viral, Bump a Smoke, Agency Spy coverage 3 days in a row Gawker/Trendhunter (Received Most Blogged),2011
- New Creatives.com, New Creation of the month and Top 5, 8X "Best of" and 3X Shortlist 2010, 2011
- Montserrat Gallery, Art show where I showed and sold my acrylic and oil paintings.